Lesson 13 is procurement
management and these are
some of the learning
objectives then for procurement.
First of all we have to understand exactly
what is procurement right and then also
understand when to outsource the work
right I mean should we outsource the work
or should we do it in-house right so we
need to understand when or rather you need
to understand for the purpose of the exam
also we're going to be talking about the
different types of contracts there's
several different types of contracts so
you need to learn about the different
types of contracts And then there's many
different procurement
management tools and artifacts
that we're going to
be talking about, right?
Some of the artifacts such as bid
documents of RFIs, RFPs, RFQs, right?
There's also things like the procurement
statement of work, the procurement
strategy, and then, you
know, many other different
tools and techniques that
we'll be covering as well.
So you need to know
all of these artifacts and
tools and techniques and
the purpose of them all.